

CHRIS ZBROJKIEWICZ

Frontend Developer

Passionate Frontend Developer with an interest in interface design and user experience.

Possesses working proficiency in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React.

Comfortable working with the command line and using Git version control.

Dedicated to the best practice technologies with a focus on responsiveness and accessibility.

PROFILE

Country

United Kingdom

Phone

<u>+44 078 35 57 5</u>7 59

Languages

English Polish

Email

chris.z@aol.com

Github

github.com/Chris-Z-85

LinkedIN

linkedin.com/in/ChrisZ85

PORTFOLIO

Website

chris-z.netlify.app



EDUCATION

2020- 2020 Full Stack Web Development

Spiced Academy, Germany

2005 - 2010 MA: English, BA: Information Technology

University of Silesia, Poland

EMPLOYMENT

2019- 2021 Teacher of English & IT

Self-employed, Germany & UK

2018 - 2019 Telematics User Support Specialist

Bosch, Germany

SKILLS

Core

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Git & Github

Additional

- React
- Redux
- SASS & BEM
- RESTful API